{
	"response_code": "0",
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Chickens can live without a head.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Science & Nature",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		}
	]
}